what if you could actually double or
triple your impact of your coaching or
course business while staying unique to
your voice and style using AI here's the
truth AI is not brand new it's been
around for a while but most people don't
know how to use it the right way and so
I want to show you in this video the
ways that we are teaching our clients to
use AI the best tools to use that you
can use and how simple it is to actually
get personalized unique sounding Just
Like You video content audio content
written content sales copy social media
posts that come out of AI in the way
that I'm using it in my workflow for
those of you haven't met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski for the last 21 years
I've been building online coaching and
course businesses to over 10 million a
year in profit my business right now we
are a multi figure business and I want
to take you through exactly how we're
using AI to get there my journey with AI
started using one of the first tools
that came on the market called Jasper Ai
and now we know obviously chat GPT
popped on the scene but there's all
these different AI tools out there how
do we know exactly which ones to use
listen I get it you're skeptical
possibly about using AI you don't want
it to take your voice away you don't
want it to sound like a robot you don't
want it to feel inauthentic and the
truth is a lot of the ways that a lot of
people use AI out there just don't hit
the mark they missed the mark they're
terrible it looks terrible it it doesn't
work out well and so I want to show show
you the tools that we're using and the
best ways to accomplish this chat GPT
while it's amazing and currently it's
actually free you can get access to it
just by going to chat gp.com it's
limited in the free version that you can
use and so there's actually a different
tool that I actually recommend that most
of my clients use it's paid but it's
cheaper than anything else that's out
there and if you look it up it's called
chat llm chat llm is only $10 a month
and it gives you all of the different AI
algorithms that are out there so there's
a lot of different tools that are on the
market and how do you know which ones to
use chat llm actually solves that for
you by allowing you to Simply utilize
all of the different algorithms in one
platform now again how do you know which
ones to use here's the way that we break
it down and I've tested all of these out
I use it in all of our marketing is that
they have different purposes GPT 40 is
the Swiss army knife one of the best
ones for doing sales copy Claude is a
little bit better at email marketing and
llama is better for Instagram or
Facebook posts that's basically what
we've discovered now there's a new
algorithm out there called 01 and 01
preview it's actually pretty cool for
brainstorming and coming up with a lot
of ideas but we're not going to go too
deep into that right now I just want to
show you how you can use this in your
business like my client Tiffany when she
first started using AI she was
floundering struggling to know exactly
what to say how to actually Market
herself how to talk and communicate her
message to people and just by simply
following some of the strategies that we
teach inside of my coaching program my
client growth accelerator she was able
to be able to launch her offer get it
out there and start marketing her
business quickly we've been using AI for
the last couple of years and we were
able to help one of our clients Rick use
AI to scale his business to over $10
million by taking input of who are his
clients what do they want creating
models around okay here's the
storytelling framework that we want to
to re people with and then Distributing
that back into the sales copy and the
messaging with the artificial
intelligence so this might be a lot this
might be a little bit of a fire hose for
you but I think you're going to get a
lot of value out of this video where I'm
going to break down exactly the best
ways to use AI how to make sure that it
actually sounds like you and how to not
miss it when you are using it how to not
make mistakes that a lot of people make
okay one of my favorite ways to do this
is by utilizing train transcripts and
here's what's awesome about the
transcript world it's gotten a lot
easier to do transcripts number one the
easiest way to do transcripts is on
YouTube Anytime you upload a YouTube
video and I'll tell you this every video
that's on YouTube has this they are
there are transcripts to every single
video on YouTube so like if I pull up
this video from alexos right here if I
pull up this video from Alex heros right
here I can actually pull up the full
transcript of his video and here's the
cool part about it chat llm has the
ability to ask questions of YouTube
videos this is one of the most amazing
features that they've included in this
and you can utilize different AI
algorithms to Simply take a YouTube link
bring it into chat llm and you can go
right here under more video and it says
analyze a video so here's how we how we
do it break break down for me the top 10
topics in this in this video and write a
summary of the most unique action action
steps someone should take by the way
this isn't even my video this is just a
video that's on there but what we're
able to do is we're able to use chat llm
to be able to identify what is in the
video it's going to analyze it it's
going to watch it it's going to
understand it and this is the really
really cool part about using chat llm is
that it has all of these really cool
tools that you don't get from inside of
Simply using chat GPT so right here we
can see the video is discussing about
delegation communication uh setting
deadlines motivation removing blocks
unique action steps make sure that you
clarify expectations now let's say that
we want to take this take this topic
right here from the video and expand
upon it into 10 unique social media post
ideas and what I want to do is I want to
actually flip the algorithm over to use
llama so that it actually uses llama to
answer this question to create social
media post ideas based on that here are
10 unique ideas that expand upon this
idea how to boost employee morale with
feedback loops regular feedback loops
increase employee satisfaction the power
of positive reinforcement so again the
video that we pulled in was all
about managing 500 employees and that
might not be relevant to you but that's
a topic that a I don't even teach at all
in my business but I'm able to pull that
video in here and come up with ideas for
Content simply by pulling a video from
an expert that's on YouTube and then
having the algorithms be able inside of
AI to tell me ideas of what to use so
this is just one of the use cases of how
we use chat llm and how we use AI to be
able to solve problems for us and come
up with ideas now how do you make this
actually sound like you well here's the
really cool part about it is that you're
able to take transcripts if you have
some video content of you talking you're
able to take transcripts of your own
video content and be able to turn that
around into a tone of voice be able to
use for your videos so I have on this
YouTube channel a ton of great videos
I'm going to just pull in this one that
I did here the other day and I want to
pull in this video we're going to create
a new chat we're going to have it
analyze my tone of voice on this
analyze the tone of voice in detail
in in this video and write it
out
write a description out in a way that
can be used to tell an AI agent how to
talk and and and by the way you don't
have to spell perfectly when you use AI
how to talk and communicate just like me
okay so there's the video right there
and let's use to do this llama is a
great algorithm that meta created to be
able to come up with this um maybe we
could also try it with gp4 we could try
it with any number of the different
algorithms that are on here you're going
to get a different response based on the
algorithms and that's one of the reasons
why I love using uh this tool with chat
llm because it gives us a lot of great
opportunities and ideas of what we can
take our prompts it anal izes it and it
can do a lot of great things for us so
it actually took some time to come up
with a step-by-step plan of what it's
going to do and then it's analyzing the
video to come up with the tone of voice
Pace language tone markers and things
like that okay so now what I can do is I
can take this tone detail right here
this is actually really really cool I
didn't even know what it was going to
create here but this is awesome because
what this is doing is it's replicating
the way that I communicate the way that
I talk now if I copy this over here
I'm going to copy this tone response
right here I'm now going to go over to
this video idea right here and I'm going
to take one of the video ideas that this
is going to create okay let's create one
about the power of positive
reinforcement okay so we're going to do
this now and I'm going to say write me a
social media post
about based on the
following tone okay so I copied my tone
of voice I told it what to make it about
and now it's going to go to work by
creating a social media Post in that
tone of voice for that here's a tone of
voice that replicates Jeremiah hey
coaches and course creators let's talk
about the power of feedback loops we
often think of feedback as a way to
correct issues but what if I told you
it's also a powerful tool for positive
reinforcement Behavior a simple thank
you or acknowledging can go a long way
to motivating your team but that
literally sounds like how I would say it
that's awesome and I think that's really
cool because you can even use that to
come up with ideas for your own video
content uh you can use that to come up
with ideas for your uh landing pages and
sales copy and things like that and so
what we've done with AI is we've been
using AI tools like chat GPT like llama
like Claude and all of that to be able
to communicate with our clients and
actually get our message out there when
you're launching your business when
you're reaching clients you have to know
who are you talking to what are the
problems that you solve and these are
the real ways that I believe that
coaches can actually to use AI is by
diving deeper into what are the things
that they actually want to accomplish in
their marketing efforts so let's say
that you work with let's just choose a
couple of ideas in fact let's just go to
work with AI and have some fun with this
watch we're going to come up with some
new ideas here and let's use the
algorithm of Claude Sonet to come up
with this actually you know what let's
try search llm search llm is a sort of a
perplexity clone which is really really
cool and I was testing this out to come
up with some ideas and so we can do is
we can go like this watch come up with
some ideas for
me on the top 100 niches that are
successful and profitable for online
coaches Consultants or course creators
so you can use AI to brainstorm with
this and what search llm is doing is
look it's actually pulling up search
articles from the internet as well as
videos video cont content news articles
and different topics on finding what are
the best ways to find a niche and now
it's giving us an output of these Niche
ideas okay so I said 100 it only gave me
10 can you generate me 100 ideas based
on
this
okay and again we might need to pull in
a different algorithm to take these idea
nope there we go it's pulling up a 100
of them that's awesome so what this is
doing is this gives us a 100 un unique
ideas that you could create a coaching
business around let's say that you do
Fitness and Nutrition coaching all right
Fitness and Nutrition coaching let's
come up with generate me and I want to
use search llm because it's searching
the internet for ideas generate me 50
sub niches
for by searching what is out there and
this is why I love using this tool
because you can really go between
different ways of using the AI search
llm if you want to find what's out there
it's really fast at finding those
different ideas so look at this this is
like it it literally went to work to
find a lot of different ways that people
are doing uh fitness and health coaching
Boutique spin Studios
CrossFit uh mobility and movement
clinics functional fitness for
seniors awesome let's go dive into and
let's use Claude here and let's say okay
okay okay so we got to switch between
Claude and search llm let's go over here
profitable niches for coaches I'm going
to copy this to the clipboard you can
see this is a copy to the clipboard
we're going to go over to Claude and
we're going to say brainstorm for
me 20 coaching program ideas and detail
out what those coaching programs will
accomplish okay so let's say you're just
in the stages of trying to figure out
what are your coaching program ideas
what this is doing is this gives us
ideas for how we can turn this into
different coaching programs and what
you're actually going to accomplish with
your clients so this is really really
cool let's just pick one of these right
here again nutrition and weight loss
coaching we're going to provide
personalized meal plans educate clients
on proper nutrition and Portion Control
now if we go
into um gp40 because it's one of the
best at doing this generate me a sales
letter for a free lead magnet that will
lead people to purchase a program on
this topic so we're copying the ideas
that it gives us back into this for this
and then we're telling the AI to
generate us some sales copy for this are
you tired of trying diet after diet only
to find yourself back at square one do
you dream of achieving your weight loss
goals without sacrificing your favorite
foods and feeling deprived in this free
guide you'll discover a personalized
meal plan nut ntion and Portion Control
emotional eating Solutions now here's
one of the ways that we might want to
brainstorm this what are 20 ideas for
lead magnets that I might promote out
there to this audience based on the
above but are different please
brainstorm okay and what I may do is I
may Reas the
question of actually no these are
actually really great ideas right here
guides to healthy eating balancing your
weekly meal prep planner weight loss uh
debunked let's dive deeper into using
the idea of having more energy and being
able to accomplish more in your life
attached to nutrition and
possibly gut health so let's say that
you want to dive into that
and change up the lead magnet ideas for
this
here are 20 ideas energizing meal plan
morning routine okay and now this is
where we want to switch over to once you
have a lot of different data that is
generated right here because we've gone
through a lot of different ideas I'm
going to switch it over to 01 preview
and I'm going to ask it this based on
the above generate
me unique lead magnets I
I can
promote for a 40 minute training to
generate leads on my email
list based on the above act as an expert
in online marketing lead generation and
understand who the target client is okay
so o1 preview it's a bit of a more
advanced algorithm that's out there and
maybe at the time you're watching this
video it's not going to be in preview
mode it might be in a more advanced mode
but it's going to take everything that
we've generated and it has this thinking
mode where it takes a longer time to
think about the response but it's going
to give us some really really great
unique ideas that we can come up with
and these are just a few of the ways
that you can use AI in your business as
a coach as a mentor to be able to come
up with lead magnet ideas to be able to
generate ways that you want to reach
your clients and to be able to grow your
email list and ultimately build trust
with people
so let's see what kind of outputs that
this came up with right here here are
some of the ideas that it generated for
us wow that's a lot of ideas all right
unlock unlimited energy free masterclass
registration offer a 40-minute training
on this directly address their desire
for more energy you could do an energy
enhancement starter kit personalized
energy assessment and action plan a 5day
energy boost email course or a challenge
the ultimate guide of beating fatigue
naturally that's actually pretty great
right there all right exclusive video
through three energy draining three
foods that are draining your energy so
actually you could combine these three
ideas you don't need to just take one
and now let's turn this turn this into a
sales letter for a free training based
on the following as a lead magnet write
some sales copy for this
okay you have exceeded the limits of the
01 preview that's okay all right so it's
switching to 01 mini now which is okay
because 01 mini is going to be able to
base this off of what is above there for
this let's see how this
looks all right are you constantly
battling fatigue struggling to keep up
with your daily tasks feel like your
energy reserves are running dry you're
not alone many people find themselves
exhausted despite trying various diets
imagine waking up each morning feeling
refreshed and energized ready to conquer
your day we're excited to invite you to
this free 40-minute training boost your
energy naturally through gut Health
Nutrition the gut energy connection
common causes of fatigue practical steps
to overcome fatigue that's not all here
are some bonuses The Ultimate Guide to
beating fatigue naturally exclusive
video the top three energy draining
Foods energy boosting recipe pack why
you should attend this that's actually
pretty good and that's a great idea for
an offer that you could come up with in
your business all right now here's the
last thing that I I want to ask it map
out for me an outline for this 40 minute
training based on the tone of voice
below okay so now what I can do is I can
take the tone of voice that it generated
I can take the tone analysis that it
gave
me and I can give this as the tone of
voice have GPT 40 adjust this and come
up with this all right welcome
introduction setting the tone
understanding the gut energy connection
the science behind gut health and energy
practical steps to enhance your energy
long-term strategies for enhanced energy
uh and then a conclusion and call the
action and then this is where you would
invite somebody to join you as a part of
your program as a part of what you do
what you offer and what you work with
clients in and listen this is something
that we do with our clients all the time
inside of my client growth accelerator
is I work with our clients every single
week on their offers on how they create
landing pages their sales copy their ads
I review stuff with them we rewrite the
sales copy together and so if you want
to become a part of that you can
actually check out the waiting list for
our client growth accelerator below we
also have free trainings all the time
that you can join and become a part of
with us to watch and to dial in inside
of your business so if you want to know
how to use AI the right way this is just
a few of the things that SC are just
scratching the surface on the way that
we use AI to come up with ideas in our
business as you can tell we've already
come up up with based on this Niche this
idea for a health coaching business some
ideas for a 40-minute video that would
be a powerful training that would
generate leads in inside of this
business we can come up with ideas for a
coaching program to lead people to Let's
actually do that next generate me
ideas for a coaching program that I can
sell for $197 a month based on the above
and map out all the features of the
program and maybe we want to use 01 mini
again for this to try this one out
because it's it's going to think about
it it's going to process this and it's
going to come up with these ideas for
our coaching
program if you're a coach if you're a
mentor and you're not using AI here's
the thing is that unfortunately all of
your competitors are using Ai and
they're going to become successful and
LeapFrog You by simply just using your
brain unfortunately now ai has become at
as important to marketing as a
calculator is to an accountant and it's
a great tool that we can use to
brainstorm our own ideas now you need to
be able to direct it and steer it and
come up with ideas but it's able to
accomplish far greater than you'd ever
imagine when you start to use it and so
again I'd encourage you if you just want
to play around with it come up with you
use a free chat GPT account and play
with it but if you want to really dive
deep into using these different
algorithms in these different ways of
using them chat llm is one of the great
tools for this so here's a program that
it created for us an idea energy revive
ultimate gut nutrition coaching here's a
comprehensive month-to-month coaching
program to help individuals restore and
sustain their energy levels we have
customized meal plan adaptive adjustment
portion control guidance all right now
let's
let's let's adjust this specifically for
people who may have
experienced uh eating disorders and are
turned off by
the
dieting approach above right that's a
great thing that we want to do and this
is how you can steer the AI to make the
content even better for you for you make
this
tailored towards women uh 30 to
55 and make it fun and exciting in the
sales copy tone of
voice all right so now it's going to go
to work and it's going to come up with
some ideas on how to make it more fun
and exciting specifically for somebody
who might have experienced eating
disorders and they're turned off by the
dieting approach and so this is where
you're able to steer the AI to really
come up with what your target client is
going to resonate with and here's one of
the most important things if you're
using AI in your business you need to
understand what your target client cares
about you need you need to understand
what drives them what motivates them
what they really really are into one of
my favorite books on sales copyrighting
is The Ultimate Sales letter by Dan
Kennedy right here and he talks about
this in the first chapter what are the
smart Market diagnosis questions what
keeps them awake at night what are they
afraid of what are they angry about what
are their top three daily frustrations
what are the trends that are occurring
in their life what do they secretly and
ardently desire the most what are their
built-in biases do they have their own
language who else is selling to them and
from that what we're able to do is we're
able to dial in exactly how to
communicate this to our prospects and to
our clients now something that I've
actually put together is on my website
there we have a free chat
GPT prompt document and really it's an
AI prompt document is what it is if you
go to Jeremiah Kowski decom you'll find
this free chat GPT down prompt download
and really it's just you can use it for
AI not just for chat GPT it can be used
for any AI algorithm you go grab this
it's a Google doc and what we have is
we've generated uh multiple prompts that
you can use to list out the pain points
and the problems come up with the
Epiphany Bridge salesletter
questionnaire outcome and results
generator and if you grab these and and
actually
drop these in you can have it go through
step by step to actually create some
sales copy using this in your business
okay let's let's take a look at this
right here this is coming up with some
ideas for us let's switch this back over
to gp40 and let's have it generate the
following based on these
steps we're going to paste all all the
six steps in
there and we're going to have it
generate initial step one write a sales
letter
list out the pain points Epiphany Bridge
we're going to have it go through the
sales letter questionnaire understanding
the client pain points we're going to
have it come up with an outcome that's
generated from this we're going to write
this based on the storytelling sales
letter framework and so here's how it's
going to go through this draft sales
letter are you tired of feeling drained
and exhausted no matter how much you eat
right or exercise I know what it's like
I've been there to struggling with low
energy and a constant pressure of
dieting can feel like an endless cycle
so you can see how it was able to adjust
to the nuances that we were telling it
to able to create something that's more
joyful and less based on diet or coming
up with just limiting the amount of food
that you're eating now we're going to
dive even deeper into this we're going
to we're going to go step by step
through this uh it looks like it wasn't
able to actually go step by step through
it so let's take each of the individual
prompts and break
down what are the pain points let's
let's grab this right here we're going
to go back to our prompt
document the o1 preview is really good
at at doing this but if we grab the
prompt document right here able to go
through this we're going to have this
generate For
Us customer insights they're struggling
with constant fatigue low energy levels
skepticism about another program and and
and by the way you're going to want to
past these individually in here to come
up with this in the best way you're
going to have it generate more deeper
ideas about who you're helping how
you're helping them and ways that you
want to express this you're constantly
battling fatigue feeling trapped by
restrictive dieting it's frustrating to
feel
exhausted okay we have emotions but
after buying dream outcome and we're
going to go down the list through each
of these what is The Epiphany Bridge The
Epiphany Bridge generates for
us exactly what the outcome is that
comes from this identify the main
problem that is solved okay main problem
that's solved is address in the sales OU
constant fatigue low energy levels
transformation from the program a few
years ago this is is creating a
fictional backstory of somebody who
might have been dealing with these
problems because what this is going to
do is it's going to pull us back into
the emotion much better to generate
outputs from this by pasting these
individually into here okay so now it's
going through each section uh key
setbacks constant fatigue restrictive
dieting balancing lifestyle and we're
getting clearer and clearer on exactly
how we want to communic unicate with our
Prospect from this okay we're going to
do the results outcome generator right
here this is one of my favorite ones
because leading with the result is much
better than leading with pain points
this is the desire this is the dream
desired outcome that somebody's going to
have as they go through this okay it's
going to create uh let's see meet Lisa
42-year-old marketing executive mother
two before joining she struggled with
constant fatigue increase energy levels
joyful relationship with food balanced
lifestyle morning routine transformation
career growth family and social life
emotional resilience vision for the
future she continues to thrive in all
aspects of her life so that's exactly
what it is now we're going to pull in
the storytelling sales framework and
there's two things that we have here
number one it's going to base us on
issue problem share an empathy story and
then we're going to rewrite it in the
tone of Sandy Kowski now if you notice
Sandy Kowski that's the same name last
name as I have that's actually my mom's
name and my mom is Sandy Kowski right
here her and I worked together during my
career to actually scale her business a
real change.com to be able to help
people grow their wealth and as well as
their finances and there's a tone of
voice that AI is actually trained on
based on the work that we did together
Sandy no longer coaches people in
business focuses more on health Fitness
and stocks and I am actually a
consultant to her business helping her
grow this using these exact strategies
using artificial intelligence to be able
to communicate all of these ideas to our
prospects all right are you tired of
feeling drained and exhausted no matter
how much you try to eat or exercise I
know what it's like I've been there too
few years ago I was caught in the Trap
endless diets fatigue juggling demanding
career family responsibilities the
pressure to maintain a perfect diet
stressed me out let me share a little
bit of my story I was desperate for
change I discover the transformtive
power of gut health and intuitive
nutrition okay how to boost your energy
naturally reserve your spot let's see
are you done feeling tired all the time
I totally get it and this is where the
Sandy tone really comes into play are
you done feeling tired all the time I
totally get it I've been in your shoes
the endless cycle of diets and fatigue
can be overwhelming but guess what
there's a way out of it and it's way
more fun than you think let me take you
back a bit you're few years ago I in the
same rut low energy constant dieting
feeling like I was missing out on life
this is exciting the way that this is
written I stumbled upon the magic of gut
health and joyful eating it changed
everything so now what this is doing is
is pulling people into this radiant
energy approach that we've been able to
process with the AI to create an offer
for us that we can come up with if we
want to now we can switch over to llama
and we can say generate four Facebook ad
ideas based on the above use the Pas
copy framework so it's able to use llama
pull these ideas in generate some
Facebook ads copy for us and then we can
use this to Market if we're going to be
doing stuff with Facebook ads copy by
the way we have a free class right now
you can find it in the descript
description below this video all about
using Facebook ads to grow your business
this is an incredible class that I
recently launched on how we're using AI
to do this this is just one of the
pieces on how we do that in that
training I walk you through how we use
AI to Target the right people the right
way using Facebook ads and i' highly
recommend you check out that training
it's right here feeling drained uh you
could use an image of a natural
landscape photo a forest a mountain
range are you tired of feeling exhausted
all the time struggling to get through
your day slump of energy picture of a
person looking tired stressed resonate
with the audience's feelings of
exhaustion vibrant energetic photo Shing
engaging Outdoors all right so check
this out here's another fun thing that
we can do with the AI if we click on
this little tab here under image you can
actually generate images based on some
of these ideas that it's creating and
it's not going to use the Llama engine
it's actually using what's called flux
Pro one flux Pro one allows us to
generate really high quality
photorealistic images and that's why I
love using Abacus chat llm is because it
provides us with so much ability to
really dial in and create incredible
images that we can use in our business
let's take this image right here Middle
Eastern that's funny okay um can you
make can and you can you can adjust it
can you make the image above more photo
realistic and show the person's face
okay so now it's GNA actually take the
image and it's going to give us a more
photo realistic image here's another
image right there oh this one was with
Dolly this one is with flux Pro cool so
it's going to make something that's a
little bit more photo realistic show the
person's face that you that we could use
as part of our marketing images or you
could use these as Facebook ad images if
you're marketing using Facebook ads okay
this one's generated with Dolly again
that's not very photo realistic let's
see what it can generate with uh flux
Pro flux Pro is going to be a lot more
photo realistic right here that's
amazing that's a that's a beautiful
photo she looks vibrant excited
happy and look it it's a photorealistic
image that's so awesome you could use
this clip this and use that as an
advertisement image or as an image on
your sales page so if you're Marketing
in your business and you're building it
using AI you can see is incredible such
an incredible tool that you can use I'm
going to leave a link below that you can
try out chat llm check it out use it I
think I think it's one of the best tools
that's out there for using AI I think
it's really refined I think they've
taken a lot of the different stuff
that's in the other tools that are out
there and brought them into one place
that you just pay one low fee of $10 a
month and you get access to all of these
great things that you can do inside of
it so make sure to check that out now
the other thing too is this is that if
you want to take this a step further and
you want to work with me you want me to
become a part of your success strategy
in your business have me come alongside
you to help you build your business
create your offers create your landing
pages and close more sales because
that's the most important part about it
I'd love for you to jump into our client
growth accelerator program and here's
why inside of our program what we focus
on more than anything else are these
four pillars right here that are most
important to us we help you break
down exactly how
to find your
Niche write your sales copy optimize
your content ads and funnels and master
the skills of sales these four things
are the most important aspect if you are
a coach course creator Mentor online to
be able to get more clients because
without knowing who you're talking to in
your Niche without communicating it in a
powerful way without selling in a way
that works without optimizing it you're
going to lose money and time and then
you got to learn how to master those
sales skills I can do that with you
inside of our accelerator program and so
I'd love for you to get on the waiting
list for this jump in when we open the
doors to our accelerator program and
work with us so that you can have more
persuasive messaging instead of it being
super complicated so that you can have
massive impact instead of low impact and
so that you can have consistent cash
flow in your business this is exactly
what we've done and worked with our
clients to generate multiple six and
seven figures in their businesses and
how we've built multiple businesses to
the eight figure Mark in this industry
to create financial and time freedom for
ourselves and our clients the
accelerator program I believe is one of
the best programs that are out there our
clients it not just me it's not just my
opinion and so jump in work with us come
on board and we'd love to get you
success and results all right this is
jeremi Kowski signing out be sure to
subscribe follow us for more videos
we'll talk soon have a good one